Billy Byers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Full Scores (Box 1-35)
  - [Notebook], Notebook which came with the collection, inventorying most of its contents. (Box 35)
Opening Hamill, Dorothy
Opening ‘77 Lane, Abbe
Opening 1977 Prowse, Juliet
Opening cont. Newley, Anthony
Opening number Prowse, Juliet
Opening titles Steve and Eydie
Opening titles Baryshnikov on Broadway
Opening... Calucci’s Dept. T.V. film
Opening.... Hanna-Barbera
Opening-closing Crosby, Bing
Orange color sky Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Orange colored sky The Farmer’s Daughter
An ordinary couple Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
Our day will come Raney, Sue
Our love is here to stay Kelly, Gene
Our love is here - overture Steve and Eydie
Our love is here to stay Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Overture 76 Gaynor, Mitzi
Overture 79 Vereen, Ben
Overture, Short Minnelli, Liza
Pass that peace pipe Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
People will say we’re in love Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy see Oklahoma medley
Personality Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
Personality Sinatra, Nancy
Pick yourself up —
Pick-a-little, talk–a-little Jones, Shirley see Music Man - medley
Picks her up Hamlisch, Marvin
Pine-apple rag Denver, John
Placement info/Placement 2-b The Music Scene
Places medley Sinatra, Nancy
Play a simple melody Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Play a simple melody continued Minnelli, Liza
Play a simple melody Minnelli, Liza see I wanna listen to rag
Player play on Anthony Curtis prod.
Playin’ with aim Hamlisch, Marvin
Playtime b.g. Andrews, Julie
Please don’t leave me Raff, Reneé
Pop goes the disco Newley, Anthony
Prelude to a kiss Eckstine, Billy
Pretty woman Basie, Count
Put your dreams away for another day Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Puttin’ on the ritz Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
Puttin’ on the ritz Lambert, Hugh
Pyramid montage Run America live tv ‘78
Queen from Moline MacLoed, Gavin
Quest Rubins, Paula
A quiet thing - new ending Minnelli, Liza
Ragtime nightingale Hamlisch, Marvin
Rain and sun medley Sinatra, Nancy
Raindrops keep falling on my head Raney, Sue
Rainy days and Mondays Sinatra, Nancy see Rain and sun medley
Razz ma tazz me Honey & Sis
Razzle dazzle Prowse, Juliet see Opening 1977
Razzle-dazzle bows Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Reach out and touch TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
Reach out and touch Helmsley & Weeks
Reachin’ for the stars Helmsley &Weeks
Reaching for the sky Warwick, Dionne
Religious medley ‘73 McKuen, Rod
Remember Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Remembering Eckstine, Billy
Rialto ripples Hamlisch, Marvin
Rich Tailor - bridge and button The Music Scene
Rio medley Ann-Margret
Road to Mandalay Basie, Count
The road to Morocco Martin Show, Tony see Travlin’ medley part I
Rodgers and Hart medley Ross, Diana
Roll over Beethoven The Music Scene
Roots Vereen, Ben
Roses of Picardy — see That’s entertainment
Roumania Grey, Joel
Rubber ball The Osmonds
Runnin’ wild Three Girls Three see Wild medley
Running boog Run America live tv ‘78
Running for fun and profit Vereen, Ben
Running shuffle Run America live tv ‘78
Running theme Run America live tv ‘78
Salute to the Olympians Run America live tv ‘78
Same old something The Music Scene
San Francisco Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Sassy and Billy Eckstine Vaughan, Sarah
Saturday night Basie, Count
Saturday night is the loneliest night of.... Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Say it isn’t so Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Say it with music Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Say it with music - underscore Steve and Eydie
Scoreboard part III Gaynor, Mitzi
The sea gull McKuen, Rod
The secret of Christmas Andrews, Julie
Send in the clowns Twiggy
Sentimental journey Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
September of my years Ross, Diana
Sergeant Pepper’s Lonely Heart’s Club Band Scott & David see Sixties medley
77 Sunset Strip ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
Seventy-six trombones Jones, Shirley see Music Man - medley
Severinsen/Armstrong suite Severinsen, Doc
Shades of today Noel, Dick
Shake a hand McKuen, Rod see Religious medley ‘73
Shaking the blues away Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Shalom Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Shangri-la Basie, Count
Shangri-la bows Lane, Abbe
Shangri-la bows —
She even woke me up to say goodbye The Music Scene
She’ll be comin’ round the mountain Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
She’s a lady (2) Falana, Lola
Shine on harvest moon Minnelli, Liza
Show biz medley Ann-Margret
Show Boat part II Ann-Margret
Show Boat pt 3 Ann-Margret
Show boat sequence part II Ann-Margret
Show stoppers, Intro Baryshnikov on Broadwa
Sidewalks of New York Newley, Anthony see Opening cont.
Sighs of the times Mateo, Pete and Beverly Layne/Layme
Since I fell for you Three Girls Three
Since I fell for you Springfield, Dusty
Since I met you baby The Music Scene
Since you’ve asked McKuen, Rod
Sing - music Streisand, Barbra
Sing, sing, sing Hanna-Barbera
Sing, sing, sing Minnelli, Liza
Singers medley ABC 25th anniversary
Sit down you’re rocking the boat Reese, Della
Six months long Ann-Margret
Sixties medley Scott & David
Slap that bass Lambert, Hugh and Nancy Sinatra
Sleighride Crosby, Bing see Christmas medley
The slender thread Eckstine, Billy
Slipped disco Honey & Sis
Smile Newley, Anthony
Smile Anton, Susan see Smile medley
Smile and show your dimple Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Smile medley Anton, Susan
Smile - Mexicali/dysko Lewis, Jerry
Smiling faces/Have a little talk Uggams, Leslie
So what! Meeza, Lee
Soft lights and sweet music Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Soldier Cronin, Kei
Soldier in the rain Raney, Sue
Soliloquy Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
Solo dance Welch, Raquel
Some people Gaynor, Mitzi
Somebody loves me Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Someone to watch over me Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Something beyond Yarborough, Glenn
Something - Hound dog - Lola... Jones, Tom
Something in your smile Meeza, Lee
Something tells me Hines, Mimi
Something to dance about Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Something’s coming–opening Chakiris, George
Something’s missin’ Welch, Raquel
Sometimes they fall Yarborough, Glenn
Sometimes when we Uggams, Leslie
Somewhere Manhattans see Lean on me
Somewhere over the rainbow Adams, Edie
Somewhere over the rainbow Hamill, Dorothy see Opening
Song for my mother Hadjidakis, Manos
Song is ended - bows Steve and Eydie
Song opener revised Smith, Keely
Sophisticated lady Rawls, Lou see Ellington medley (fix)
Sound of music opening /underscore Andrews, Julie
The sound of music Smith, Keely see Song opener revised
South of the border Reese, Della
South Pacific entracte - S.P. medley Gaynor, Mitzi
South Sea medley Lamour, Dorothy
Spaceships transposing Carpenters
Speak to the sky Smith, Keely
Special people Lovell, Marilyn
Spinning wheel Lewis, Jerry
Spring cleaning play on/off Gaynor, Mitzi
Spring is here The Supremes
Stagger Lee Meeza, Lee
Stars and stripes Andrews, Julie
Starting today —
Starting tomorrow Raff, Reneé
Still Eckstein, Lulita
Stop time rag Hamlisch, Marvin
Stormy weather Sinatra, Nancy see Rain and sun medley
The story teller Newley, Anthony
Stravinsk bridge and button The Music Scene
Street of dreams Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Strike up the band Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Sugar blues - Fifth of Beethoven Gaynor, Mitzi
The sugar opera The Music Scene
Sugar, sugar The Music Scene
Summertime Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Sunday McKuen, Rod
A Sunday kind of love Reese, Della
Sunday, Monday or always Lamour, Dorothy see South Sea medley
Sunday mornin’ Raney, Sue
Sunshine on my shoulder TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
Surrey with the fringe on top Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy see Oklahoma medley
Swanee Ann-Margret see Show boat part II
Swanee Ann-Margret see Show boat pt 3
Swanee Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
Swanee Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Sweet beginning Newley, Anthony
Sweet Caroline Lewis, Jerry
Sweet gentle love Raney, Sue
Sweet inspiration - intro Streisand, Barbra
Sweet Lord - Happy day Falana, Lola
S'wonderful Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
Symphony #5: L.V. Beethoven Gaynor, Mitzi
TV concert section Ann-Margret
Ta-ra-ra-boom-der-e Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Take my word Raney, Sue
Take your girlie to the movies (closing) Ford Special
Takin’ care of business Gaynor, Mitzi
Talk to the animals Bushkin, Joe
Tangerine Reese, Della
The tango Gaynor, Mitzi
Tell me whad I say McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
Tell me why Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
Le Temps Minnelli, Liza
Temptation Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Tenderly Prysock, Arthur
Tenderly Vaughan, Sarah see Sassy and Billy Eckstine
Tennis shoe blues Basie, Count
Tetanus sets in Basie, Count
Thank you Carpenters
Thanks for giving her a list Hamlisch, Marvin
That lovin’ feeling The Osmonds
That’s all Basie, Count
That’s entertainment —
That’s life Smith, Keely
The song is ended but the melody lingers on Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
Theatre B/E Honey & Sis
Theatre land Baryshnikov on Broadway
Them there eyes Gaynor, Mitzi
There! I’ve said it again Vinton, Bobby see Hit medley ‘77
There’s no business like show business Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
There’s no business like show business Hopkins, Mary
They call the wind Maria Hartman, David
They can’t take that away from me Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
They can’t take that away from me Luft, Lorna
They can’t take that away from me Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
They can’t take that away from me Andrews, Julie see Gershwin medley
They say it’s wonderful Heatherton, Joey see Falling ballad medley
They say it’s wonderful Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
They’re playing our song - medley Steve and Eydie
They’re playing our song - reprise Steve and Eydie
Things bright and beautiful Yarborough, Glenn
Thirties opening Hawn, Goldie
This guy’s in love with you Hartman, David
This is all I ask Hartman, David
This is the night - opening Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
This is your life - Help Uggams, Leslie
This is your life Carroll, Diahann
This love of mine Basie, Count
This minute Carroll, Diahann
This nearly was mine Reese, Della
This one’s for you Three Girls Three
Thoroughly modern Millie Bushkin, Joe
Those wedding bells shall not ring out Randall, Tony
Those were the days Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Thou swell Ross, Diana see Rodgers and Hart medley
Three girls revised, Intro to Ann-Margret
[Three girls three] 3 girls 3 Three Girls Three
Three is a crowd Honey & Sis
Three music scene buttons The Music Scene
The thrill is gone King, B. B.
Through the eyes of love Boston Pops
Thursday McKuen, Rod
Tie a yellow ribbon Crosby, Bing
Till love touches your life Falana, Lola see Academy 71 medley
Till there was you Jones, Shirley see Music Man - medley
Time after time McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
Time and distance added parts McKuen, Rod
A time for love Williams, Andy
Time was Damone, Vic see Nearness of you
To all the girls Vinton, Bobby
To be a rockette Radio City Music Hall Special
To make you smile again Ladd, Cheryl
Today I found a friend McKuen, Rod
Tommy overture/rescore Ann-Margret
Tomorrow is a brand new day Anthony Curtis prod.
Tomorrow is a lovely day Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
Too close for comfort Reese, Della
Too marvelous for words Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Toot toot tootsie Crosby, Bing see Everything old is new again
Top hat Franchi, Sergio
Touch me in the morning TV Critics Awards 1977 see Contemporary medley
The town that won’t sleep Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
Toyland Crosby, Bing see Christmas medley
Tra la la - symphony Steve and Eydie
Tradition Franchi, Sergio
Transition... Dancing Machine
Travlin’ medley part I Martin Show, Tony
Try a little tenderness Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Tuesday, Tuesday Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Twelfth Street intro Gaynor, Mitzi
The twelth of never Falana, Lola
Two of a kind Minnelli, Liza
Typo TV Critics Awards 1977
Tzena, Tzena, Tzena Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot II
Tzena, Tzena, Tzena Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
Up on the roof - rescore Springfield, Dusty
Up to now Elliot, [Mama] Cass
Upstairs downstairs [theme] TV Critics Awards 1977 see Miscellaneous cues
Vaya con dios Raney, Sue
Vegas parade.... Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
The Vegetarian Bushkin, Joe
The very thought of you Eckstine, Billy
Violets for your furs Sinatra, Nancy and Frank Jr.
Volare —
Les Wages sont commencer Hadjidakis, Manos
Wait till the sun shines Willie Raney, Sue
Wait till you see her The Supremes
Wait until dark Raney, Sue
Waitin’ for the Robert E. Lee Ann-Margret see Show biz medley
Waitin’ for the Robert E. Lee Ann-Margret see Show boat sequence part II
Walk right in Basie, Count
Walking happy Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Walking happy Bushkin, Joe
Walking in the park Lewis, Jerry
Waltz with my shadow Hadjidakis, Manos
Waltzin’ the jack Manchester, Melissa
Was I a fool/Was I a merry go round Mateo, Pete and Beverly Layne/Layme
Watch the roses grow McKuen, Rod
Watch what happens Damone, Vic
Watermelon man Basie, Count
The way we were Hope, Bob
The way we were Byner, John
The way you look tonight Lane, Abbe see Celebrity medley
The way you look tonight Reese, Della
We can see the sun Brown Rice
We who are about to diet Gaynor, Mitzi
We’ll be together again Raney, Sue
We’re in the money Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
We’ve only just begun ABC 25th anniversary see Singers medley
We’ve only just begun Falana, Lola see Academy 71 medley
Webb medley Prowse, Juliet
Wee small hours Reese, Della
Welcome back ABC 25th anniversary see Welk-Lennon Sisters medley
Welk-Lennon Sisters medley ABC 25th anniversary
Well did you ever [sic] Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
Wey Marie Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot #2
What a difference a day made Falana, Lola
What a fool believes Boston Pops
What about today Falana, Lola
What are you doing the rest of your life Carroll, Diahann
What did I have Ross, Diana
What did I have that I don’t have? Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
What I did for love Steve and Eydie see They’re playing our song....
What I did for love Alberghetti, Anna Maria
What makes a dance feel so good Anthony Curtis prod.
What the world needs now Lewis, Jerry see Fanfare - What the world....
What’ll I do? Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
What’s the use of breaking The Music Scene
Whatever Lola wants Jones, Tom see Something - Hound dog - Lola
When I fall in love Heatherton, Joey see Falling ballad medley
When I look in your eyes Bushkin, Joe
When I lost you Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
When I’m not near the one I love.... Greco, Buddy
When my ship comes in McKuen, Rod see McKuen retrospective 73
When oh when Raney, Sue
When the children are asleep Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
When the midnight choo-choo leaves.... Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
When the saints go marching in Severinsen, Doc see Severinsen/Armstrong suite
When the sun comes out Sinatra, Nancy see Rain and sun medley
When you’re smiling/I want to be happy Gaynor, Mitzi
Where am I going Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Where does love go/No one will ever know Raney, Sue
Where or when Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Where or when Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
Where’s the love Raney, Sue
Whistling in the dark Andrews, Julie see Mancini medley
White Christmas Ann-Margret see Christmas 1973
White dove Brown Rice
Who am I? Lovell, Marilyn
Who are those guys? Ann-Margret
Who taught her everything? Ann-Margret
Why can’t I touch you? Cardinal, Vin
Wichita lineman Sinatra, Nancy see Places medley
Wien Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot IV
Wild medley Three Girls Three
Wilkommen Grey, Joel see Cabaret
Wilkommen bows —
Will he like me — see Dear Friend
Will you love me, tomorrow? McKuen, Rod
Winchester Cathedral Gaynor, Mitzi see Melting pot III
The windmills of your mind Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
Windmills of your mind-On the apple tree Raney, Sue
A winner/A loser TV Critics Awards 1977
Witchcraft Lucien, John
With a song in my heart Smith, Keely see Song opener revised
With plenty of money and you Hawn, Goldie see Thirties opening
Without a song Smith, Keely see Song opener revised
Without a worry in the world Yarborough, Glenn
Without me Raney, Sue
Without you Lewis, Jerry
Wives and lovers Four Tops
World of ballet... MacLaine, Shirley
Would you believe McRae, Carmen
Wouldn’t that be nice Newley, Anthony
Write pagan rights —
Y.M.C.A. Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.
Yankee doodle dandy Mr. Dugan
Yankee doodle reprise —
Yes I can —
Yester-me Wonder, Stevie
Yesterday Eckstine, Billy
You and I Owen, Michael
You are so beautiful to me Jeffries, Fran
You are the sunshine of my life Jeffries, Fran see Isn’t she lovely - sunshine medley
You can have him Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
You could drive a person crazy Three Girls Three
You don’t know what love is Vaughan, Sarah see Sassy and Billy Eckstine
You keep coming back like a song Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
You make me feel so young Basie, Count and Frank Sinatra
You never done it like that Ann-Margret
You stepped out of a dream ABC 25th anniversary
You’d be surprised Steve and Eydie see Concert/leftover medley
You’ll never know Morrow, Buddy
You’ll never walk alone Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
You’re a grand old flag Franchi, Sergio see George M. Cohan medley
You’re a grand old flag Honey & Sis
You’re blase — see That’s entertainment
You’re gonna hear from me Ann-Margret
You’re gonna hear from me Smith, Keely
You’re just in love Steve and Eydie see Berlin on Broadway
You’ve got to be carefully taught Rodgers/Hart tv special see Family of man medley
You’ve got to be carefully taught Gaynor, Mitzi see South Pacific...medley
Your cheatin’ heart Basie, Count